Digital asset trading is going to explode.
The digital asset trading future has the ability to completely disrupt trading.
All assets in the future could be traded between individuals, between entities.
At the moment, digital assets are largely being focused on currencies.
But I think going forward, there's lots of different ways in which digital assets can be monetized.
Once you accept that most assets around the world can be tokenized,
you start seeing the adoption in everyday walk of life activities,
you realize that there is something big happening here.
The digital asset space has really matured in the last 12 months,
and proof of that is a person like myself coming from the hedge fund industry,
taking an interest in the space and thinking, how do we get involved?
The reason that institutions are not so involved in crypto trading at the moment
is the lack of transparency within the marketplace.
They need to see processes and systems which either are regulated or act as if they are,
and are really, really robust on the technology, their custody,
and the way they perform, particularly with regard to compliance.
If the crypto market became regulated, institutional investors would flock towards it.
The size of the market is massive, and their clients feel that they need to get a share of this.
Archax is aiming to be a top-tier, regulated, institutional-focused digital asset exchange
that differentiates itself from the current players
by being purely focused on institutions and their clients.
We want to be a respected, institutional-grade player that is headquartered in the City of London,
and we want to build an exchange and have a custody solution that is institutional-grade and segregated,
where institutions and accredited investors feel comfortable buying and selling digital currencies.
Archax is a team of credible financial individuals
that have worked in a regulated environment their whole career.
The vision for Archax is to bring the traditional trading experience
into the digital asset, straight crypto world.
The key excitement at the moment is how digital asset trading is going to integrate
with the current financial infrastructure.
We're dealing with tier-one software providers that have been providing matching engines
to the traditional financial markets for many years.
Our platform is going to be transparent, it's going to be delivered in an extremely regulatory, safe, secure way.
All of the participants on the exchange will have gone through anti-money laundering,
and know your client checks.
Archax is very exciting because it's in one of the fastest moving industries in the world.
Anyone that you speak to starts being sceptical, they gradually get more excited,
and before you know it they're fully engaged in the space and start to see the possibilities.
The future is massive. This will grow and grow and grow.
It's an incredibly exciting space to be in.
We have the product, we have the people, we have the systems, we have the thinking,
and we have the vision that we need to get there.
We've seen exchanges in the digital asset space pave the way for where we are today,
and that's very important.
For the institutions to come in, we need evolution.
Archax is the next stage of that evolution.